These taste just like chewed gum. I'm
not sure what you guys are talking about
when you guys say that the brand new
Built Bars literally taste just like
gum. These right here, guys, definitely
have like a candy taste to them. If you
guys have not seen them before, this is
going to be part of their sour line. You
guys have the little sour coating right
there on the top that has like sprinkles
and stuff, which is sour. You guys have
this candy outside instead of like a
chocolaty outside like the other Built
Bars. And of course, you guys are
getting the marshmallowy inside. When it
comes to the taste,
you guys ain't getting anything close to
like a chewing gum. I'm not sure where
that came from. Definitely uncalled for,
but if you guys do want to go ahead and
check out the brand new Built Bars,
specifically in the pink lemonade
squeeze flavor, you guys can get them
right now on the TikTok shop for a
really good price before they sell out
by clicking on that link right below
this video.